[
	{
        "id": "air",
        "subject": "Air",
        "questions": [
            {
                "questionText": "What is the runway slope limit?",
                "answerA": "+/- 5 %",
                "answerB": "+/- 2 %",
                "answerC": "+/- 3 %",
                "answerD": "+/- 4 %",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the maximum take-off weight for the A320?",
                "answerA": "79000",
                "answerB": "78000",
                "answerC": "77000",
                "answerD": "75000",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the maximum landing weight for the A320?",
                "answerA": "67000",
                "answerB": "66000",
                "answerC": "65000",
                "answerD": "60000",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the maximum altitude for take-off and landing?",
                "answerA": "9800 feet",
                "answerB": "7800 feet",
                "answerC": "9200 feet",
                "answerD": "9000 feet",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the maximum fuel temperature?",
                "answerA": "54C",
                "answerB": "56C",
                "answerC": "52C",
                "answerD": "55C",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the maximum cabin altitude differential pressure?",
                "answerA": "8.00 psi",
                "answerB": "9.10 psi",
                "answerC": "7.50 psi",
                "answerD": "8.60 psi",
                "correctAnswer": 4,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "Concerning the APU what is the maximum APU EGT during start above 25000 ft?",
                "answerA": "900 C",
                "answerB": "825 C",
                "answerC": "982 C",
                "answerD": "882 C",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the maximum wind for passenger door operation?",
                "answerA": "60kts",
                "answerB": "65kts",
                "answerC": "55kts",
                "answerD": "68kts",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "Maximum wind conditions for CAT II / III Automatic , landing and rollout:",
                "answerA": "Headwind: 30 knots • Tailwind: 10 knots • Crosswind: 20 knots",
                "answerB": "Headwind: 25 knots • Tailwind: 10 knots • Crosswind: 20 knots",
                "answerC": "Headwind: 35 knots • Tailwind: 10 knots • Crosswind: 20 knots",
                "answerD": "Headwind: 30 knots • Tailwind: 10 knots • Crosswind: 25 knots",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the maximum speed that the wipers can be operated?",
                "answerA": "250kts",
                "answerB": "230kts",
                "answerC": "200kts",
                "answerD": "180kts",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the Minimum Altitude for autopilot engagement during takeoff and manual go-around?",
                "answerA": "Take off with SRS mode: 100ft AGL and at least 5 seconds after liftoff",
                "answerB": "Take off with SRS mode: 120ft AGL and at least 5 seconds after liftoff",
                "answerC": "Take off with SRS mode: 100ft AGL and at least 15 seconds after liftoff",
                "answerD": "Take off with SRS mode: 50ft AGL and at least 5 seconds after liftoff",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the maximum altitude for concerning the APU air condition & pressurization in dual pack operation?",
                "answerA": "14000ft",
                "answerB": "12500ft",
                "answerC": "10000ft",
                "answerD": "15000ft",
                "correctAnswer": 4,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What are the Maneuver Limit Load Factors with slats and flaps extended?",
                "answerA": "0.0 to +2.0 G's for slats and flaps extended",
                "answerB": "1.0 to +2.0 G's for slats and flaps extended",
                "answerC": "0.0 to +1.5 G's for slats and flaps extended",
                "answerD": "0.5 to +2.0 G's for slats and flaps extended",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the Maximum Operating speed Vmo/Mmo?",
                "answerA": "VMO - 350 Kts / MMO -.81 Mach",
                "answerB": "VMO - 350 Kts / MMO -.82 Mach",
                "answerC": "VMO - 350 Kts / MMO -.83 Mach",
                "answerD": "VMO - 340 Kts / MMO -.82 Mach",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the maximum Landing Gear Tire Speed?",
                "answerA": "The landing gear tires are limited to a ground speed of 195 knots",
                "answerB": "The landing gear tires are limited to a ground speed of 205 knots",
                "answerC": "The landing gear tires are limited to a ground speed of 215 knots",
                "answerD": "The landing gear tires are limited to a ground speed of 185 knots",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "The maximum and minimum glideslope angles for autoland are:",
                "answerA": "Maximum 4.25 and minimum 2.50",
                "answerB": "Maximum 4.15 and minimum 2.50",
                "answerC": "Maximum 3.15 and minimum 2.50",
                "answerD": "Maximum 3.25 and minimum 2.50",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the operating restriction for HF Radio Operation?",
                "answerA": "Do not operate in congested areas",
                "answerB": "Do not operate HF radios during refueling operations",
                "answerC": "Do not operate when VHF communication is available",
                "answerD": "Do not operate the HF in the hangar",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the maximum crosswind for NEO engine start?",
                "answerA": "25 knots",
                "answerB": "30 knots",
                "answerC": "45 knots",
                "answerD": "35 knots",
                "correctAnswer": 4,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "When is it allowed to use reverse?",
                "answerA": "It is recommended to use reverse below 70kts",
                "answerB": "On ground only",
                "answerC": "In flight",
                "answerD": "Below 10ft RA",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the maximum altitude to extend slats/flaps?",
                "answerA": "Do not extend the flaps/slats above FL100",
                "answerB": "Do not extend the flaps/slats above FL150",
                "answerC": "Do not extend the flaps/slats above FL200",
                "answerD": "Do not extend the flaps/slats above FL250",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What are the Weather Radar restrictions for use?",
                "answerA": "Do not operate the weather radar in a hangar or within 50 feet of any personnel or fuel spill",
                "answerB": "Do not operate the weather radar in a hangar or within 50 feet of any personnel or fuel spill or people",
                "answerC": "Do not operate in flight",
                "answerD": "Do not operate the weather radar in a hangar or within 60 feet of any personnel or fuel spill",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "fcom": "",
            },
            {
                "questionText": "What is the normal operating hydraulic pressure?",
                "answerA": "The normal hydraulic operating pressure is 2,000 PSI plus or minus 200 PSI",
                "answerB": "answerB”: “The normal hydraulic operating pressure is 2,500 PSI plus or minus 200 PSI",
                "answerC": "The normal hydraulic operating pressure is 3,000 PSI plus or minus 100 PSI",
                "answerD": "The normal hydraulic operating pressure is 3,000 PSI plus or minus 200 PSI",
                "correctAnswer": 4,
                "fcom": "",
            }
        ]
    },
]
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
